[{"question": " morning!", "answer": " hi! oh, how was your date last night?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " pretty good.", "answer": " oh good.  ahhh! my god, sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " okay, really good. anyway i gotta go; i&#146;m late for work.", "answer": " what-what?! you&#146;re gonna leave this person with me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah&#151;hey, don&#146;t worry, she&#146;s a terrific girl. and hey listen, could you do me a favor? when she comes out could you just mention that i&#146;m not looking for a serious relationship; that&#146;d be great.", "answer": " why?! what?! are you kidding?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " just casually slip it in, y&#146;know lay the groundwork. tell her uh, i&#146;m a loner&#151;no! an outlaw! tell her she doesn&#146;t want to get mixed up with the likes of me.", "answer": " y&#146;know what? that&#146;s a lot to remember, can&#146;t i just tell her you&#146;re a pig?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hey, i&#146;m gonna call her later! honest! oh come on, chandler used to do it! he&#146;d even make the girl pancakes! plus, he&#146;d make extras and leave &#145;em for me.", "answer": " well forget it, i&#146;m not telling that girl anything. that is not my responsibility.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " sorry about that, but i couldn&#146;t get that lock to work on the door.", "answer": " yeah, joey kinda disabled it when i moved in.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " you must be rachel, i&#146;m erin.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " hi. i don&#146;t mean this to sound like high school, but did he say anything about me?", "answer": "  would you like some pancakes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " &#133;come on! why are we here?!", "answer": " okay, okay take a guess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " the hot chicks?", "answer": " okay, okay, i was typing names into the library computer earlier, y&#146;know-y&#146;know for fun, and i typed mine in and guess what came up? my doctoral dissertation! it&#146;s here! yeah, it&#146;s right-it&#146;s right down here! in the biggest library in the university!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " wow that&#146;s actually pretty cool.", "answer": "  oh umm, there&#146;s also a book here by a woman named wendy bagina.  what is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": "  i&#146;m so sorry!", "answer": " sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " she sent the chicken back again?!", "answer": " she says it&#146;s to dry now and she wants to come back here and explain to you exactly how she wants it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": "  lucky bastard!  janice.", "answer": " how are you ms. hot shot chef with the big fancy restaurant with the best chicken ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i&#146;m fine.", "answer": "  ohh! what is that on your finger?! i&#146;m blind!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh&#133; uh&#133;", "answer": " so, who&#146;s the lucky guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh&#133;my&#133;gawd! i am so sorry sweetie, are you okay? you didn&#146;t tell her we were getting married, did you?", "answer": " well, she saw the ring.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " did she freak out?", "answer": " well, she was shocked when i told her, but then again so were most people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " right.", "answer": " well, she actually has a boyfriend y&#146;know herself, named clark. uh, she also kinda invited herself to our wedding. clark too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  you said no right?", "answer": " huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " you said no right?!", "answer": " well, she corned me! she asked if the wedding was in town! i mean, what was i supposed to do?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " lie!!! how hard is that?! the check&#146;s in the mail! oh your baby is so cute! i can&#146;t wait to read your book ross!!", "answer": " come on! so she comes to the wedding! i mean it won&#146;t be so bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " what do you think she&#146;s just gonna sit there quietly? you don&#146;t think she&#146;s gonna want to make a toast? you don&#146;t think she&#146;s gonna want to grab the microphone and sing part-time lover?!", "answer": " oh my god, she&#146;s not gonna like the chicken that night either is she?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? it&#146;s gonna be okay. y&#146;know what? she&#146;s probably not gonna even want to come.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " no! that was a lie! see how easy that was?", "answer": " so-so you would&#146;ve just lied?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yes!!", "answer": " would it really have been that easy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " yes!!!", "answer": " good, so do it saturday night because we&#146;re going to dinner with her and clark.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " hey! what&#146;s up? phoebe and rachel: hey!", "answer": " hey-hey, who&#146;s your friend?  hey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey joey!", "answer": " erin! still here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " yeah, we ended up spending the day together and had such a great time!", "answer": " why wouldn&#146;t ya? erin is great! then-then there&#146;s you guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " ohh, listen. i&#146;ve got to get going. today was great, thanks!", "answer": " i know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " bye joey.  last night was fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yeah. i&#146;ll uh, i&#146;ll call ya.", "answer": " oh and i&#146;ll call ya too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " or i&#146;ll call you!", "answer": " and call me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  okay, good to see you again.", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " bye-bye.", "answer": " bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " so, system kinda broke down huh?!", "answer": " oh joey, i&#146;m sorry i just couldn&#146;t tell her all those things you wanted me to tell her. and y&#146;know we got to talking and i&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " we want you to marry her!", "answer": " what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " she is so amazing! you have no idea.", "answer": " no idea? who do you think brought her here?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " cupid.", "answer": " joey, she&#146;s so cool. she speaks four languages.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " man, do you know what guys want!", "answer": " look joey, come on she&#146;s so perfect for you! i mean she&#146;s sweet, she-she likes baseball, and she-she had two beers at lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " my beers?! look you guys, she&#146;s a very nice girl. okay? we had a good time, but i just&#151;i don&#146;t see it going anywhere.", "answer": " yeah, but you always say that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " yeah, maybe if you gave this girl a chance it would go somewhere.", "answer": " look i&#146;m sorry you guys, i-i just don&#146;t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " whatever.", "answer": " fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " hey, don&#146;t start judging me!  huh? you&#146;re the one who&#146;s in love with her assistant!  huh? and you, you&#146;re the one having the affair with the guy who keeps the pigeons on the roof!", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " people are doing it in front of my book!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " my doctoral dissertation is in the library at school, i went to see it, and there were students makin&#146; babies right in the middle of the paleontology section!", "answer": " oh my god! did you get to see anything good?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " let me ask you something, at your school was there a like uh a place on campus where students went to uh, fool around.", "answer": " yeah, there was. it was&#151;there the corner of the library where-where all these dusty books that nobody ever read&#151;yes, there was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " great! because people kept showing up, i think it&#146;s like uh-a thing!", "answer": " now hold on a second, fifth floor against that back wall?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " all right, so we should go catch our movie.", "answer": " well now what&#146;s the rush?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i like to see the previews.  the candy.", "answer": "  oh. hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " well look who&#146;s here!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " erin.", "answer": " hey rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hi! well, we were just about to take off and see a movie. oh no!", "answer": " what&#146;s wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh phoebe, we forgot that party we have to go to.", "answer": " oh no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  what party? phoebe and rachel: a birthday party.", "answer": " who&#146;s birthday party? phoebe and rachel: allison&#146;s birthday party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": "  wait a minute! why don&#146;t you guys do something?!", "answer": "  yeah, look how that worked out. commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " excuse me. hi, i&#146;m a professor here. do you know the paleontology section, fifth floor, stack 437?", "answer": " well, yes! just give me five minutes, i just have to find someone to cover my shift.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " no! no!! no! can i speak to someone in charge please?!  the head librarian: how can i help you?", "answer": " hi, i was wondering if it is possible to increase security in the paleontology section? see i-i wrote a book up there and instead of reading it people are-are-are well, rolling around in front of it. the head librarian: we are aware of the problem you are referring too.  but as far as increasing security, i&#146;m afraid the library is very understaffed. i, i can&#146;t help you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " how did it go with erin?", "answer": " oh, unbelievable! we had the best time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " yay!! oh so, you&#146;re not, you&#146;re not mad at us anymore?", "answer": " no! no! no! you guys were totally right! this is so much better than the first time we went out. y&#146;know? that was so awkward, we were really nervous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " didn&#146;t you sleep together?", "answer": " yeah that really calms me down. and! we have so much in common! she loves sandwiches, sports, although she is a met fan, not much of an issue now but if were ever to have kids, well that&#146;s a&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  oh my god! listen to you talkin&#146; about having kids. oh my joey.  oh, please don&#146;t get married before i do.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " oh. oh i just cannot believe clark stood me up!", "answer": " he might still show up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, what are you, stupid? it&#146;s been three hours.", "answer": " is that all?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " i should just go on to happier things, okay? umm, why don&#146;t you tell about your lovely wedding?", "answer": " well actually uh, there was something we wanted to tell you about the wedding. um, it&#146;s going to be a small ceremony. uh, tiny! we&#146;re not even sure why we&#146;re having it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " it&#146;s actually going to be just family.", "answer": " oh&#133;wait&#133;you two think of me as family?! oh, i have to ask you something now and be honest; do you want me to sing careless whisper or lady in red?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " how can you say that?! the mets have no closer!", "answer": " what about benitez?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " what about game 1 of the series?", "answer": " what about shut up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " you shut up!  i love arguing with her.  i&#146;ll be right back.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " so how&#146;s it goin&#146; with joey?", "answer": " uh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " okay? wait okay, tell-tell me that you like him, please? i mean tell me that you like him.", "answer": " look, he&#146;s a really great guy and i know that you really want this to work out, but i just don&#146;t see this having a future.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " but you said that you liked him! i mean what happened?! did ya just change your mind?!", "answer": " kinda.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " then change it back!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry i&#133; it&#146;s just there&#146;s no real spark.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " no spark? didn&#146;t you sleep together?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ugh, tramp!", "answer": " does joey have any idea?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " i really don&#146;t think he does. and y&#146;know what? maybe you guys could help clue him in. y&#146;know, tell him i&#146;m-i&#146;m not interested in a serious relationship or something.", "answer": " yeah, you mean like that you&#146;re kind of a loner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " yeah! that would be great!", "answer": " yeah, and maybe that you&#146;re a real", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry?", "answer": " oh well, i guess italian isn&#146;t one of the four languages you speak.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": "  hey! you wanna go?", "answer": " yeah, let&#146;s go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay. see you guys later.", "answer": " bye guys.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah, see ya.", "answer": "  hey, thank you so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " wow. well, i guess it was cupid who brought her here.", "answer": " no, just a regular old flying dwarf.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yes? yes?! how can i help you?", "answer": " yeah, we were&#133;we were just looking around.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh-oh, you&#146;re-you&#146;re fellow scholars. what exactly were you looking for, hmm? perhaps,  perhaps dr. chester stock&#146;s musings on the smiledon californicus?", "answer": " uhh&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " ah&#133; ah&#133;get out of here!  uh, meeting someone? or-or are you just here to brush up on marion&#146;s views on evolution?", "answer": " uh, actually i find marion&#146;s views far to progressionist.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i find marion&#146;s views far to progressionist.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry, who are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " i&#146;m a professor here uh, ross&#133;geller.", "answer": " ross geller, why do i know that name? it&#146;s uh&#151;wait!  did you write this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " yes! you&#146;re the person who checked out my book?!", "answer": " y&#146;know, you look nothing like i would&#146;ve thought. you&#146;re&#133;you&#146;re so young.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " so how was, how was your date?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh, it was great! i mean we walked all around the village. we went to this ice cream place, split a milkshake, 70/30 but still&#133; and guess what, i&#146;m thinking about taking her upstate to one of those bed and breakfasts.", "answer": " oh really? she said she wants to go away with you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " no-no-no-no-no! it&#146;s a surprise, but it&#146;s gonna be tricky thought because she said she was gonna be pretty busy at work for a while. phoebe and rachel: oh no, yeah.", "answer": " jo-joey, look honey we-we need to talk okay? umm, i kinda got the feeling from her today that uh, she&#146;s not lookin&#146; for a serious relationship.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " where are you gettin&#146; this?", "answer": " well, she told me. she said she&#146;s kinda a loner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh. oh.", "answer": " joey&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " no hey rach, it&#146;s cool okay? y&#146;know i&#146;m a loner too!  right?", "answer": " hey joey, y&#146;know what? you are way to good for her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " yeah and honey i promise next time that i will just say good-bye and tell &#145;em you&#146;re not looking for a relationship.", "answer": " no! no. don&#146;t do that, just next time make sure she really likes me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " well that too.  joey?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " do you want some pancakes?", "answer": "  finally!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " what are we gonna do?", "answer": " i say we go with careless whisper.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " chandler?", "answer": "  did she see us yet? did she see us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " janice, what umm, what are you doing here?", "answer": " well umm, i thought i was going to go back to my apartment but then i just felt i couldn&#146;t really be alone tonight.  i was wondering if i could maybe stay here with you, just i really feel that i need to be with family.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  our kids are gonna call her aunt janice aren&#146;t they?", "answer": " please, it&#146;s because otherwise i really don&#146;t know what i might do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " aren&#146;t you just a tinsy bit curious?", "answer": "  do you have any tissues?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yeah, in-in-in the bathroom.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " we&#146;ll just&#133;we&#146;ll just let her stay.", "answer": " no-no-no-no, if we let her stay, she will stay forever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " kinda like your barca lounger.", "answer": " is that what you&#146;re thinking about right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i never stop thinking about it.", "answer": " hey you guys, umm do either one of you want to get in there before i take my bath.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " janice, i&#146;m sorry but umm, you can&#146;t stay here tonight.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh my god! oh my god! you have to go!", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " because chandler still has feelings for you!", "answer": " he does?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " say again?", "answer": " that&#146;s right. that&#146;s right. and that is why you can&#146;t stay here tonight. and probably why you shouldn&#146;t come to the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " feelings, such strong feelings.", "answer": " i mean, i realize that his feelings may never completely go away, but you can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}]